Guide to the Isaac Levi Papers, 1949-2014 ASP.2016.04
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Isaac Levi Papers
1949-2014
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Levi, Isaac
ASP.2016.04
51.25 Linear Feet (41 record center boxes)
The Isaac Levi Papers document the professional career of American Philosopher Isaac Levi from 1949-2014. Over the course of his career, Levi made important contributions to areas such as epistemology, philosophy of science, decision theory and the philosophy of Charles Sanders Peirce. Fruitful debate between Levi and one of his colleagues and former students, Henry E. Kyburg Jr, resulted in an approach to certain philosophical questions that has come to be known as formal epistemology. He served as doctoral advisor to numerous prominent formal philosophers, among them Horacio Arló-Costa and Teddy Seidenfeld.
Acqusition Information
Gift of Isaac Levi in 2016.
Scope and Content Notes
The Isaac Levi Papers document the academic career of American philosopher Isaac Levi, who was John Dewey Professor of Philosophy Emeritus at Columbia University. The papers contain correspondence, scholarly articles, drafts, speeches, notes, reviews and photographs related to Levi's intellectual body of work, including his contributions to decision theoretic reconstruction of epistemology and formal epistemology.
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Arrangement
The Isaac Levi Papers are arranged in four series:
Series I. Correspondence
Series II. Lectures and Speeches
Series III. Research and Reviews
Series IV. Photographs
Biography
Isaac Levi was an American philosopher who held the John Dewey Professor of Philosophy chair at Columbia University. Levi was born June 30, 1930, the son of a military chaplain whose career took the family to postings around the world; during his childhood Levi lived in many places in the United States as well as abroad; these postings included New York State, Canada, Australia, and Hot Springs, Arkansas.
Levi attended New York University as an undergraduate and received a B.A. in 1947. He then went on to earn an M.A. at Columbian which was granted in 1953. Levi was a doctoral student of Ernst Nagel at Columbia University, completing a Ph.D. entitled, Positivism and Realism in the Epistemology of Moritz Schlick in 1957 under Nagel's supervision. He also was given a Ph.D. Honorus Causa by Lund University in 1988. After spending time on the faculties of the City College of New York and Case-Western Reserve University, Levi returned to Columbia University in 1970 where he would serve for nearly four decades as a professor in the Philosophy department.
Levi's first book Gambling with Truth developed the decision theoretic reconstruction of epistemology in close relation to important 19th century pragmatist philosophers such as William James and Charles Sanders Pierce. Publishing seven books and many scholarly articles and book chapters during his career, Levi also became known for his groundbreaking work in belief revision and imprecise probability. Over the course of his career Levi made important contributions to areas such as epistemology, philosophy of science, decision theory and the philosophy of Charles Sanders Peirce. Fruitful debate between Levi and one of his colleagues and former students, Henry E. Kyburg Jr, resulted in an approach to certain philosophical questions that has come to be known as formal epistemology. Levi served as doctoral advisor to numerous academically trained philosophers, among them Horacio Arló-Costa and Teddy Seidenfeld. Levi was married to Judith Rubins for 67 years and had two sons, Jonathan and David. Isaac Levi died on December 25, 2018.
Related Material
Ernest Nagel Papers, 1925-1985, ASP.2020.01, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System.
Personal correspondence; Decision-making; Probabilities; Knowledge, Theory of; Science -- Philosophy; Statistics; Pragmatism; Epistemology; Correspondence; Levi, Isaac; Arlo-Costa, Horatio; Seidenfeld, Teddy
- Correspondence, 1949-2014; I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  Series I. Correspondence--contains forms of scholarly communications, such as articles, notes, written correspondence and information files shared between Levi and other colleagues, peers and scholars regarding various philosophical concepts and issues. Occasionally, manuscripts containing messages and marginalia that were sent to Levi and are included here, while additional manuscripts are also located in Series III. The series contains five subseries: Alphabetical Correspondence (1949-2014), Chronological Correspondence (1955-1992), Probability and Decision Theory Correspondence (c. 1950s-2007), Collaboration with Teddy Seidenfeld (1974-2014) and Collaboration with Horatio Arlo-Acosta (1990-2011). These reflect Levi's original organizational method and classes of information placed within those categories.
  - Alphabetical Correspondence, 1949-2014; 1.
    Subseries 1. Alphabetical Correspondence contains scholarly and professional correspondence files kept by Levi and organized by last name or topic.
    - Achinstein, Peter, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Ackermann, R., undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Ackoff, Russell, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Adler, Jonathan, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Adler, Jonathan, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Adler, Jonathan. Review of Bogdan, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Alanen, Lilli, 1981-1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Alchien, Armen A., undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Alchourron Carlos E., Peter Gardenfors and David Makinson, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Alchourron, Carlos E., Peter Gardenfors and David Makinson, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - All Souls College Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Allias-Ellsberg, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Allias-Ellsberg, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Almeder, Robert, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Altrichter, Ferenc, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - American Philosophical Association (APA) Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Anger, Erik, 1998-2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Anscombe, G.E.M and Aumann, R.J., 1962 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Anscombe, G.E.M., 1971 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Artnzenius, Frank, 2003-2006 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Audi, Robert, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Averill, Edward, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Avigad, Jeremy, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Azzouni, Jody, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Bacchus, Faheim, Adam J. Grove, Joseph Y. Halpern, Daphne Koller, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Banerji, R.B., 1967 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Bar-Hillel, Maya and Avishai Margalit, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Barker, Alston and Nagel, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Barnard, G.A., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Barwise, Jon and John Perry, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Basili, Marcello and Carlos Zappia, 2007-2009 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Basu, D., undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Basu, D., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Bayes, T., undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Beardman, Stephanie, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Bedau, H.A., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Bencerraf, Paul, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Berger, James O., c. 1982 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Bergson, A., undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Berka, K., 1969-1974 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Berkovitz, Joseph, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Berlin, Isiah., 1966-1988 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Bernoulli, Daniel and M.G. Kendall, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Bernoulli, Jakob, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Bernoulli, James, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Bever, Thomas G., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Bilgrami, Akeel, c. 1980s (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Bilgrami, Akeel, c. 1990s (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Bilgrami, Akeel, c. 1990s (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Bilgrami, Akeel, c. 2000s (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Bilgrami, Akeel, undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Birnbaum, Allan, c. 1970s (Box 2, Folder 1-6)
    - Birnbaum, A., "Likelihood", "Confidence Cases", "Comments on Turkey", "On Durbin's Principle", 1961-1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Birnbaum, Alan, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Birnbaum, Alan, 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Birnbaum, Alan, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
    - Birnbaum, Alan, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Black, Duncan, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Black, Max, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Blackburn, Simon, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Bochman, A., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Bogdan, Radu J., 1983 (Box 2, Folder 17-18)
    - Bovens, Luc and James Hawthorne, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Bradley, Richard, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Braithwaite, R.B., c. 1960s (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Braithwaite, Richard, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Brandom, Robert B., 1994 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Brandom, Robert, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Brody, B.A., undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Bromberger, Sylvain, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Bruce Hill, 1979-1986 (Box 2, Folder 28-29)
    - Brush, Stephen G., 1974 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Buchak, Lara, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Buchdahl, Gerd, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Burch, Robert W., 1992 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Burge, Tyler, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Burks, Arthur and Irving M. Copi, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Burks, Arthur W., c. 1960s (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Burnyeat, M.F., undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Burros, Raymond H., 1974 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Camp, Michael, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Cantwell, John, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Cardwell, Charles A., 1974-1991 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Cargile, James, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Carnap, Rudolph, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Cartwright, Nancy, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Castelo Jaquin, Domingo, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Cauman, Leigh S., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Charles Plott, c. 1973-2000 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Chaudhuri, Adhip, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Chisolm, Roderick M., 1965 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Chomsky, Noam, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Chuaqui, Rolando, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Churchman, C. West, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Cloud, Daniel, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Cochran, William G., undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Cohen, G.A., 1997 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Cohen, L Jonathan, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Cohen, Michelle and Jean-Yves Jaffray, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Collins, John, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Condorcet, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Constantini, Domenico, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Cook, Albert, 1975-1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Coolen, Frank, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Cooley, J.C., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Coppock, Paul, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Costantini, D. and U. Garibaldi, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Cox, Chana B., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Cozman, Fabio, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Craig, William, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Creary, Lewis G., 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Cresto, Eleanora, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Cumming, Robert D., 1981 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Cubit, Robin P., 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Dacy, Raymond, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Danto and Morgenbesse, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Darden, Lindley, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Daston, Rene, 1979-1983 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Dauben, Joseph W., 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Davidson, Donald, c. 1990s (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Davidson, Donald, 1964-1973 (Box 3, Folder 32-33)
    - De Finetti, Bruno, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - De la Pena, Morris H., 1991 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - DeGroot, Morris H., 1974 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Delaney, C.F., 1979 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Dempster, A.P., 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Dennett, D.C., 1978-1984 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - DeRose, Keith, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - DeRose, Keith, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Dickey, James M., 1981-1987 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Disintegration Conglomerability, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Domotor, Zoltan, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Domotor, Zoltan, 1981-1986 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Doring, Frank, 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Dorling, Jon, 1979-1990 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Douven, Igor, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Dray, undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Dubins, Lester E., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Dudman, Victor H., 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
    - Dudman, Victor H., 1990-1995 (Box 4, Folder 3-5)
    - Duggan, Timothy and Bernard Gert, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Dummet, Michael, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Ebert, Theodor, 1971-1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Edel Abraham Social Science and Value, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Edel, Abraham, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Edwards, A.W.F., 1969 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Eells, Ellery, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Efron, B., 1986 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Elga, Adam, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Elgin, Kate, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Elster, Jon on Pascal, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Elster, Jon, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Engel, Pascal, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Esfeld, Michael, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Fain, Haskell, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Fallis, Don, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Fallis, Don, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Favereau, Oliver, no date (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Feferman, Solomon, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Feigl, Herbert, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Feinberg, Gerald, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Feinberg, Joel, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Fellner, William, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Ferme, Eduardo L, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Festa, Roberto, c. 1980s (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Fetzer, James H., 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Feyerabend, P.K., undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Fiducial Probability, c. 1950s (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Field, H., undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Finch, Henry A., 1964 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Fine, Arthur, 1970-1981 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Fishburn, Peter C., 1983 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Fisk, John E., 2003 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Fitelson, Branden, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Fodor, Jerry A., 1991 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Forster, Paul D., undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Foss, J., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Frank, Jacob, undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Frankfurt, Harry G., 1964-1986 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Frankle, Charles, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Fraser, D.A.S., c. 1960s (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Friedman, Michael, 1975-1982 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Fu, Daiwe, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Fuhrmann, Andre, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Gaa, James C., 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Gadol, Eugene T., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Gaifman, Ham, 1997-2002 (Box 4, Folder 52-53)
    - Gaifman, Ham, 1997-2002 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
    - Gaifman, Ham, c. 1980s (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
    - Garber, Daniel, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Gardenfors, Peter and David Makinson, 1989-1994 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Genot, Emmanuel J., 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Geoffrey, Joseph, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Gert, Bernard, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Get Well Cards and Correspondence, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Geuss, R., undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Gibbard, Alan F., 1998 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Giere, Ronald N., c.1970s (Box 5, Folder 13-15)
    - Gigerenzer, Gerd, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Gigerenzer, Gerd, 2002-2006 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Gilles, Anthony S., 2002 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Ginsberg, Arthur, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Gintis, Herbert, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Godambe, V.P., 1976 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Godfrey-Smith, Peter, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Goe, George, 1962-1970 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Gold, Natalie, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Golding, M.P., 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Goldman, Alvin I., undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Goldstein, Michael, c. 1980s (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Good, I.J., 1951-1989 (Box 5, Folder 28-29)
    - Good, I.J., 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Good, I.J., 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Good, I.J., c. 1980s (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Goosens, William K., 1970-1975 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Gorecki, Jan, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Gorovitz, Samuel, 1966-1970 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Graham, Loren R., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Graham, Loren R., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Grandy, Richard E., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Green, Edward, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Grim, Patrick, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Gruender, David, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Grunbaum, Adolf, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Grunberg, Emile, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Grzegorczyk, Andrzej, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Guttmann, Y.M., undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - H.W. Kuhn and A.W. Tucker, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Haack, R.J., 1971 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Haack, Susan, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Haack, Susan, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Hacking, Ian, 1965-1975 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Hajek, Alan and Alex Byrne, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Halmos, P., undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Hammond, John S., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Hammond, Peter, 1976-1986 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Hampton, Jean, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Hanson, Norwood R., undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Hansson, Bengt, 1969-1974 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Hansson, Sven Ove, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Harada, Akinobu, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Hardin, Russell, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Harding, E.F., 1971 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Hardy, G.H., undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Harmon, Gilbert, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Harper, William L., 1976-1990 (Box 6, Folder 31-34)
    - Harrah, David, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Harre, R., 1970 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Harris, John H., 1981 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Hart, H.L.A., 1962 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Haurie, Allain, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Hausman, Dan, 1979-1986 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Hawthorne, Jim, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Hayek, F.A., 1996 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Hazen, Allen, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Heilig, Klaus, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Hempel, Carl G. and Paul Oppenheim, c. 1950s (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Hempel, Carl G., 1962-1988 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Henkin, Leon, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Herzberger, Hans G., 1962-1979 (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
    - Herzberger, Hans G., c. 1970s (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Hesse, M., no date (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Higginbotham, James, c. 1980s (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Hild, Matthias, 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Hild, Matthias, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Hild, Matthias, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Hildreth, Clifford, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Hilpinen, Risto, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Hilpinen, Risto, 1995-1998 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Hintikka II, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Hintikka, Jacko and Raimo Tuomela, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Hintikka, Jacko, 1963-1966 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Hintikka, Jacko, 1968-1973 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Hintikka, Jacko, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Hinzen, Wolfram, 1997-2006 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Hiz, Henry, 1984-1992 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Hockney, Donald, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Hodges, J.L. and Lehmann, E.L., undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Hodges, J.L., E.L. Lehman, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Hoff, Eberhard, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Honderich, Ted., undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Hook, Sidney, c. 1980s (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Horn, Alfred and Alfred Tarski, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Hornbach, F., undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Hornstein, Norbert, 1981-1985 (Box 7, Folder 28-29)
    - Horty, John, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Houthakker, H.S., undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Howard, Don, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
    - Howson, Colin, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Huber, Franz, 2004-2006 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Hudson, D.J., 1970 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Humberstone, I.L., 1981 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Hurley, S.L., undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Ihara, Jiro, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Inada, Ken Ichi, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Ishiguro, Hide, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Jackson, Frank, c. 1980s (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Jarret, John P., 1984 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Jeffrey, Richard C., c. 1960s-1980s (Box 8, Folder 15-16)
    - Jones, Garreth, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Joyce, James and Allan Gibbard, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Joyce, James M., 2002 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Judy's Poem for My 65th Birthday, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Kadish, Mortimer and Sanford, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Kalbfleisch, J.G. and D.A. Sprout, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Kalmar, Lazlo, no date (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Kaplan, Mark, 1979-1989 (Box 8, Folder 24-26)
    - Kasimis, Demetra, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Katz, Jerrold J., undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Kemeny, John G., c. 1950s (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Kessler, Eckhard, undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Khalidi, Muhammad Ali, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Kim, Chin-Tai, c. 1960s (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Kitcher, Phillip, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Kitcher, Phillip, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Kitcher, Phillip, undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Klein, Martin J., c. 1960s (Box 8, Folder 36-37)
    - Kohler, Eckehardt, 1971-1984 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Kolmogoroff, A., c. 1960s (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Koslow, Arnold, 1979-1996 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Koslow, Morganbesser, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Kournay, Janet A., undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Kripke, Saul, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Krips, H.J., undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Kristeller, Paul O., 1993 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Kuhn, Thomas S., 1973-1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Kuipers, Theo A.F., 1995 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Lablanc, Hugues, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Lad, Frank, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Ladd, John, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Lakatos, Imre, 1968-1970 (Box 9, Folder 11-12)
    - Lancaster, Kelvin, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Landesberg, P.T., 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Larmore, Charles, 1981-1986 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Laslie, Adele, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Latsis, Spiro, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Laudan, Larry, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Leach, James, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Lear, Jonathan, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Ledwig, Marion, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Lee, T.D., 1984 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Leeds, S.J., undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Lehman, E.L., 1970 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Lehrer, Keith (Box 9, Folder 25-26)
    - Lemmen, Charles, c. 1960s (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Leplin, Jarrett, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Levin, Samuel R., 1981 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Levin, Samuel R., c. 1950s-1980s (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Levinger, George, undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Lewis, David, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Lewis, David, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Lieberson, Jonathan, 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Lindley, D.V., c. 1950s (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Lindley, Dennis V., 1971-1981 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Lindt, Gillian, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - List, Christ and Franz Deitrich, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - List, Christian, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Loewer, Barry, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Lopez-Gonzales, Jose, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Los, Jerzy, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Loui, Ronald P., undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Luchins, Edith H., undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Lugg, Andrew, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Lyon, Paul, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Macklin, Ruth (Songs), undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Macklin, Ruth, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Maher, Patrick, 1985-1987 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Makinson, David and James Hawthorne, 2007-2008 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Makinson, David, 1984-1993 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Makinson, David, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Makinson, David, c. 1990s (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Malament, David B., 1981 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Marcel, Richter, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 15)